<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Hey Love</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">המושב 2</singer>
        <writer>יהודה סלומון</writer>
        <composer>רון אניאלו</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Hey Love</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>I had a golden life, everything and anything a man could ever want. But I had to risk it all so I could have something worthwhile. You touch me and I crumble to the dust. I gotta get back on my feet again. Give me something to hold, I want someone to trust.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza"/>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>Hey love, hey love, hey love. I’m tired of being down. Everywhere I turn I see someone running scared. Time is running out. Yesterday’s news is a million miles away. You move</l>
          <l>me and my life begins again. All I really want to think about is something that’s going to last.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>Keep me where you are. </l>
          <l>Keep me where you are. </l>
          <l>Keep me where you are. </l>
          <l>Keep me where you are.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>When I’m falling and twisting and losing and drifting too far, keep me where you are. When I’m falling and twisting and losing and drifting too far, keep me where you are.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="6" type="stanza">
          <l>Halleluya ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo. Halleluya ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo. Halleluya ki tov,</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="7" type="stanza">
          <l>ki le’olam chasdo. Halleluya ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo. Hodu l’Hashem ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="8" type="stanza">
          <l>Halleluya ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo. Halleluya ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo. Hodu l’Hashem ki tov, ki le’olam chasdo.</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
