<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>The Italian job</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">התקווה 6</singer>
        <writer>עמרי גליקמן</writer>
        <composer>עמרי גליקמן</composer>
        <album>כל יום מחדש</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>The Italian job</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>Early early in the morning</l>
          <l> me woke up with no reason me woke up with no warning</l>
          <l>Me gial hand me the phone she sais somebody is callin</l>
          <l>A who that want fi badda so early in the morning?</l>
          <l>It's the lady from the bank she said I need to come</l>
          <l>There's nuff paperwork that needs to be done</l>
          <l>The early we start the early we done</l>
          <l>So bring your money money Mr. you better run over ya so</l>
        </lg>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>Babylon took I from my girlfriend on a early Friday morning yeah</l>
          <l>I never ever ever want to leave her again even if the earth is falling yeah</l>
          <l>Babylon steal I from my woman on a early Friday morning yeah</l>
          <l>I never ever ever want to leave her again no I never want to go</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>The bank lady said she's a big fan</l>
          <l>		She aksed me:"how you doin'"? me told her :"I'm fine"</l>
          <l>We will soon take the papers I need you to sign</l>
          <l>But take a step back now and stand inna the line</l>
          <l>"how rude!" and so me stood it wasn't that quick</l>
          <l>Me know say Babylon can make you feel weak</l>
          <l>After a minute or two me felt homesick</l>
          <l>And so me called me girlfriend but she doesn't want to speak anymore…</l>
        </lg>
        <lg Chorus="yes" number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>Babylon took I from my girlfriend...</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>After one hour, two, three </l>
          <l>I was a bank prisoner I wasn't free</l>
          <l>And then finally it was my turn</l>
          <l>Why did me woke up early? Why do I never learn?</l>
          <l>You know the lady from the bank she's pretty and kind</l>
          <l>She said I wasn't easy for all of them to find</l>
          <l>She took a likkle peace of paper she said: "we're almost done"</l>
          <l>I just need you to sign here and here it's for my daughter and son…  ""</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>