<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Blue Eyed Shadow</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">הדרה לוין</singer>
        <writer>הדרה לוין</writer>
        <composer>הדרה לוין</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Blue Eyed Shadow</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>You keep on calling me all that late at night. </l>
          <l>I really don’t know what’s on you mind. I just want to get laid, kinda sweet and safe, by your side. </l>
          <l>But you’re beating around with your new music collection. </l>
          <l>There’s something about your late night voice </l>
          <l>that doesn’t feel right. I’m scared to be wondering aloud, </l>
          <l>do you love me, do you love me not. I’m letting you talk. </l>
          <l>You get scared and annoyed. </l>
          <l>I’m moving my Dylan around, </l>
          <l>getting sick of my voice. </l>
          <l>You’re playing awful hard-to-get with my words. </l>
          <l>I just gotta get laid tonight. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>You remember everything about last night, I kinda like it. </l>
          <l>You didn’t like Hedwig, you didn’t get me at all. </l>
          <l>I realize how far you can go, </l>
          <l>20 years get in the way of getting laid, </l>
          <l>washed in mad music, tripping ahead. </l>
          <l>Dylan, Bright Eyes, Beck, Ryan Adams, Pete Yorn </l>
          <l>and a Badly Drawn Boy. </l>
          <l>I wonder what really went wrong on your zone </l>
          <l>that you sound so alone at your home. </l>
          <l>You’ve been tracking down songs, smiling away, </l>
          <l>with just the wrong accent on the wrong face, on the wrong day. </l>
          <l>I just wanna get laid tonight. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>I know just what you’re thinking. I’m thinking just the same. </l>
          <l>Got some problems saying what I want at your face, </l>
          <l>but I’m working on it. I’m taking some French. </l>
          <l>I manage an army of hi-tech boom-brains, and I’m doing allright. </l>
          <l>You got a great voice, dancing there all on your own. Kinda cool. Everyone’s getting married, hard-core famous, music biz faces, </l>
          <l>great shiny places and all. What a great show and a perfect day. </l>
          <l>You look like a top-model. </l>
          <l>I’m just a working class hero with something to say. Well, don’t block the way of your bright shining spark. </l>
          <l>Trust me when I tell you that I love you so hard. </l>
          <l>Ooh, but I don’t. I get scared. </l>
          <l>Morning breaks and I’m kinda running away. </l>
          <l>Out of your quiet peace of town, right down my little piece of hell. Back in the city where no one can tell, right from wrong, </l>
          <l>natural shine from intangible gel. </l>
          <l>I’m doing what I want, acting what I am. </l>
          <l>And no one ever really messes up with my name. </l>
          <l>If I tell you I love you, please don’t get me wrong. </l>
          <l>My music gets to choose my top-ten pleasures of this world</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
