<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Too Much Of A Good Thing</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">הדרה לוין</singer>
        <writer>הדרה לוין</writer>
        <composer>הדרה לוין</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Too Much Of A Good Thing</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>Too sweet to be true, and so fucking new, to sweet to fall in love with you, so absolutely not like anyone before, </l>
          <l>I’ve fallen way yonder for many a beautiful boy. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>If yesterday you came my way, I wouldnt’ve seen the magic. </l>
          <l>If yesterday you called my name, I wouldnt’ve heard your voice. </l>
          <l>Something foreign in the air has twisted all the rules. </l>
          <l>The game became so young again, and babe, it’s bringing back the blues. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>I try to be precise, more real, more true with words to you. But running out of waters, I get stuck with loving you, Just like that. Just like that. My mind is running blank. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>I used to love the young &amp; blazing, mad &amp; amazing, hard &amp; somewhat sweetly plasticating, masticating, tempting to the lips &amp; bones, American style hip-hop &amp; all </l>
          <l>with some neo laid-back chic of some passive-alternative soul. But I never loved anyone more than Rock &amp; Roll. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>Let me put it this way, for 20 years or so, </l>
          <l>I never got laid by anyone older in this world. </l>
          <l>You move me on the soft side, I’m used to tripping wild. </l>
          <l>I’m scared to be tamed, but I’m taking this ride. </l>
          <l>People say it’s time </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="6" type="stanza">
          <l>Words come easy when you’re messing with your mind. </l>
          <l>It’s just another morning where you left your skin behind. </l>
          <l>Sea-salt air, a gentle buzz, the inner city wake up call. </l>
          <l>And I would give it all to you, but you always wanted more. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="7" type="stanza">
          <l>Your CK perfume is the mild of the set. </l>
          <l>It never lasts on anyone else longer than your self. </l>
          <l>I sniff it while it lingers, like a mad dog under your spell. </l>
          <l>But too much of a good thing will get you straight to Hell </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="8" type="stanza">
          <l>BUT I NEVER LET YOU DOWN, why don’t you stay some with me, to the end of time</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
