<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Little Man</title>
        <singer classification="band">הדג נחש</singer>
        <writer>שאנן סטריט</writer>
        <composer>missing</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Little Man</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>Yo! come from the holiest place on earth </l>
          <l>and still i don't believe in shit </l>
          <l>sticking my music in you for whatever it's worth </l>
          <l>you can use it or refuse it whatever you see fit </l>
          <l>got me an appetite for party tonite </l>
          <l>so i think i might go out despite slight fright </l>
          <l>pretending i'm alright gonna drown my fears </l>
          <l>intending to delight my soul down a beer </l>
          <l>gotta drive thru various random checkpoints </l>
          <l>they be looking thru my pockets for weapons n' joints </l>
          <l>at the entrance to the club i'm sure that you know this </l>
          <l>searched once again for explosives n' roaches </l>
          <l>all this just so i can get loaded </l>
          <l>where a whole bunch of buddies of mine exploded </l>
          <l>n' left me on this planet on my own </l>
          <l>fuck it- i think i'm gonna stay home, get stoned. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>I'm just a little man </l>
          <l>I come from the Middle East </l>
          <l>I wanna be a free man </l>
          <l>I ain't no gangsta no </l>
          <l>I'm just a little man </l>
          <l>coming from the Middle East </l>
          <l>I wanna be a free man </l>
          <l>I ain't no gangsta no </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>If i were a bird i'd fly high in the sky </l>
          <l>and dump a big ass turd all over all religious </l>
          <l>sites </l>
          <l>like an activist get other birds to join in too </l>
          <l>til' everything would actually be covered in pooh </l>
          <l>so many close calls so many times i could've died </l>
          <l>now my brain cells feel like falafel- deep fried </l>
          <l>this ain't no fairy tale ain't no mother goose </l>
          <l>one thing's for sure - when hell really breaks loose </l>
          <l>i'm gonna be loungin' in the box seats </l>
          <l>residing in the town whre three religions meet </l>
          <l>and when they decide to clash </l>
          <l>n' burn this mother fuckin' shit hole to the ash </l>
          <l>i won't pass on the opportunity given to me </l>
          <l>to light a fat ass hash doobie that'll really screw me </l>
          <l>get real smashed... kick back... </l>
          <l>while i watch all types of pathetic fanatics attack. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>I'm just a little man </l>
          <l>coming from the Middle East </l>
          <l>I wanna be a free man </l>
          <l>I ain't no gangsta no</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
