<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Home 3</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">שי 360</singer>
        <writer>שי 360</writer>
        <composer>שי 360</composer>
        <album>כולם רוצים את האמת</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Home</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>One love, one life, let’s get together and feel alright</l>
          <l>One Place, one home. If you want to make it where you’re going…</l>
          <l>You got to know where you’re from.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>I was told, “united we stand divided we fall", I guess that how we really stayed alive through it all</l>
          <l>We made it through the struggle, through the blood and the tears, getting stronger with the times, stronger with the years</l>
          <l>I found out: taglit, that’s your birthright. Right of birth to see the place that make us unite</l>
          <l>To see where it started, to connect and to feel. To soul search, find our roots and to know that it’s real</l>
          <l>As it all comes together like the words of a song. 6 years in the making, 1nk0qe0qmco0vgpqtkju11Blessed with the help of more fortunate few. For this gift that we got we are thankful to you</l>
          <l>We all live in different places, with different faces but there is only one home and you could never replace it </l>
          <l>It’s more than a state, it’s a state of mind that gives ears to the deaf and eyes to the blind</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>אין כמו לראות בעיניים ולהאמין, אין כמו להיות במקום כדי להבין</l>
          <l>זה חלום של כל כך הרבה שרק רוצים לחזור למקור ולשורשים</l>
          <l>זה לגלות ולחזק גם את הזהות. זה לגלות שפה זה בית שמה זה גלות</l>
          <l>לגלות את הנפש והיהדות. בחיפוש העצמי זוהי המהות</l>
          <l>זו תגלית: 1nk0qe0qmco0vgpqtkju11מתוכם רבים שבים רבים עולים. אלינו מצטרפים, חלום הם מגשימים</l>
          <l>מי שלא חווה את זה גם כן לא ידע. מאז... "אם תרצו אין זו אגדה"</l>
          <l>היום זה לא חלום ולא אשליה, לשנה הבאה בירושלים הבנויה!</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza"/>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
