<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>Restoring My Soul</title>
        <singer classification="unknown">שטר</singer>
        <writer>שטר</writer>
        <composer>שטר</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>Restoring My Soul</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>Chorus: I wanna thank the king for restoring my soul in the morning when the sun is yawning.  Thank the king for restoring my soul, restoring my soul. x2 </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>Verse 1:</l>
          <l>what you is, what you into.  I can't pretend to, pretend its me who rocks this instramental.  This sentiment to extend to those that HaKadosh Baruch Hu extends his hand to. Better bet you, in the nexus net from death.  He does come to protect you.  Without the question he's gonna catch you, bless you, dress you, take the next step and ressurect you. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>Chorus: Modeh ani lifanecha melech chai v'kayam, sh'chezarta bi nishmati, chemla raba emunasecha x2 I wanna thank the king for restoring my soul in the morning when the sun is yawning.  Thank the king for </l>
          <l>restoring my soul, restoring my soul. x2 </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>Verse 2:</l>
          <l>I breath deep when my soul retreats.  I sleep a slumber numbered 1 b'shesheem.  Prophecy coupled with a touch of death.  With the next step lets clense our hands of this impurity.  Let him nurish me with food house home and funishing.  Certainly true betuhchon creates complete security.  Precise in devise supports my life more than surgery.</l>
          <l>Stepping on in with real conception and let you learn the lesson.  Burn with the words and let them churn and make you yern up in your mental.  They're gonna get ya, you better bet ya.  You think  you're something right here you haven't heard a word i've said to you.  Right?  Bringing you back on track with facts and stats.  Imagine that your stature backwards background bring you back down then your sat down.  Yeah!  And bring you back down, yeah!  You'll see the fat crown yeah.  I'm nothing right so clear no fear a fact now. </l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>Chorus: Modeh ani lifanecha melech chai v'kayam, sh'chezarty bi nishmati, chemla raba emunasecha x2 I wanna thank the king for restoring my soul in the morning when the sun is yawning.  Thank the king for restoring my soul, restoring my soul.</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
