<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>February</title>
        <singer classification="male singer">שאנן סטריט</singer>
        <writer>שאנן סטריט</writer>
        <composer>שלומי שבן</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>February</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down soon- that's clear</l>
          <l>a memory of some sort a child's tear</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down before too long</l>
          <l>maybe a photo, i don't know, maybe this song</l>
          <l>february can be real brutal</l>
          <l>but this year we're getting lots of sunny days</l>
          <l>life has its way of pampering you sometimes</l>
          <l>in meaningless n' stupid n' pathetic sort of ways</l>
          <l>i’ve had some newfound creativity flowing through me</l>
          <l>a buzz of opinions and ideas gushing through me</l>
          <l>most days n' most nights are a lot less gloomy</l>
          <l>it’s like i look at myself and i see a new me</l>
          <l>well maybe 'new' isn't exactly what i mean</l>
          <l>because it's more like i feel that what i’m actually seeing</l>
          <l>is a freer me an easier me not a bitter me a sweeter me</l>
          <l>the kind of me i could have been if this wouldn't have happened or if</l>
          <l>my heart was tin</l>
          <l>but then again in the back of my head</l>
          <l>i know this can't last there’s a giant slope ahead</l>
          <l>it’s all a matter of when i begin the descent</l>
          <l>to the depths that no one can mend</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down soon- that's clear</l>
          <l>a memory of some sort a child's tear</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down before too long</l>
          <l>maybe a photo, i don't know, maybe this song, maybe this song</l>
          <l>going to a party later tonight</l>
          <l>don’t really want to but i should be polite</l>
          <l>to the people who invited me- friends of mine</l>
          <l>sometimes i have pictures of them in my mind</l>
          <l>at your funeral all red eyed n' teary</l>
          <l>tonight their gonna be all chit chat n' cheery</l>
          <l>at your funeral with stubble n' a trembling bottom lip</l>
          <l>tonight at the party they'll all attempt to look hip</l>
          <l>hop around, maybe dance a little</l>
          <l>have a drink eye a woman and advance a little</l>
          <l>do just what i would have done once upon a time</l>
          <l>before the mutant cell you were hosting committed its crime</l>
          <l>before it picked you in your prime- but that's enough!</l>
          <l>please! please no more of this stuff!</l>
          <l>these thoughts and myself just like bonnie n' clyde</l>
          <l>the party's starting i better get ready so i don't miss my ride</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down soon- that's clear</l>
          <l>a memory of some sort a child's tear</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down before too long</l>
          <l>maybe a photo, i don't know, maybe this...</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down soon that's clear</l>
          <l>a menu a street sign a child's tear</l>
          <l>something’s gonna drag me down before too long</l>
          <l>maybe this party tonight who knows... maybe this song, probably this song.</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
