<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
    <fileDesc>
      <titleStmt>
        <title>July</title>
        <singer classification="male singer">שאנן סטריט</singer>
        <writer>שאנן סטריט</writer>
        <composer>חוה אלברשטיין</composer>
        <album>missing</album>
      </titleStmt>
      <publicationStmt>
        <date>2016</date>
      <publisher>Yoav Cohen and Maya Ben Tov, Ben-Gurion University</publisher></publicationStmt>
      <sourceDesc>
        <p>The website SongLyrics: http://songlyrics.co.il</p>
      </sourceDesc>
    </fileDesc>
    <profileDesc>
      <langUsage>
        <language ident="he">Hebrew</language>
      </langUsage>
    </profileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
    <body>
      <lg type="song lyrics">
        <head>July</head>
        <lg number="1" type="stanza">
          <l>A dozen months ago I started this poetry diary project thing</l>
          <l>I felt my feet falling and i knew i had to cling</l>
          <l>to the only things in this world that are a part of my heart</l>
          <l>my wife n' my kids of course but also my art</l>
          <l>que sera sera what will be? no clue!</l>
          <l>let the world dictate my life and my pen followed through</l>
          <l>never lied never tried to hide what i felt i said</l>
          <l>when it was time to cry i cried, time to bleed I bled</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="2" type="stanza">
          <l>n' am I happy now? nope. don't use the word hope</l>
          <l>optimism seems to slip between my fingers like soap</l>
          <l>but something very deep in me can now see things differently</l>
          <l>cuz now at least I know I can cope.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="3" type="stanza">
          <l>followed this almost scientific epic almost religiously  </l>
          <l>at times found myself wishing I could take this less seriously</l>
          <l>in the midst of raw agony the search for something esthetic </l>
          <l>didn't come naturally sometimes I felt quite pathetic</l>
          <l>killing the screens like I did spilling the beans like I did</l>
          <l>remaining unshielded unprotected like a kid</l>
          <l>on a long long journey towards youth</l>
          <l>every step taking me both closer and farther from truth</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="4" type="stanza">
          <l>n' am i happy now? nope. don't use the word hope</l>
          <l>optimism seems to slip between my fingers like soap</l>
          <l>but something very deep in me can now see things differently</l>
          <l>cuz now at least i know i can cope.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="5" type="stanza">
          <l>listening closely to my baby I started thinking</l>
          <l>how horrible it would be to not hear his tiny breath</l>
          <l>every moment in my day contains some nothing</l>
          <l>every instant in my life carries death</l>
          <l>I'll never forget i had a little sister</l>
          <l>never cease to love and miss her</l>
          <l>have thoughts concerning her for as long as I live</l>
          <l>imaginations contemplations various kinds of "what if..."</l>
          <l>are destined to be part of me forever, however</l>
          <l>time made me clever and i now realize</l>
          <l>I've got a whole lot more than just tears in these eyes</l>
          <l>I've got a whole lot more than just tears in my eyes</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="6" type="stanza">
          <l>n' am I happy now? nope. don't use the word hope</l>
          <l>optimism seems to slip between my fingers like soap</l>
          <l>but something very deep in me does now see things differently</l>
          <l>cuz now, I know I can cope.</l>
        </lg>
        <lg number="7" type="stanza">
          <l>a dozen months ago I started this poetry diary project thing </l>
          <l>I was at an all time low, hanging from very thin string</l>
          <l>one year later- a proud father of two boys</l>
          <l>occupied insanely with diapers and toys</l>
          <l>I know I'm in a better place cuz shit!</l>
          <l>life showed me it's ugliest side and I faced it</l>
          <l>only once in a while I get weak in the knees</l>
          <l>Tova Yael Streett rest in peace, please.</l>
        </lg>
      </lg>
    </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
